question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In \'Star Trek\', Klingons are commonly referred to as \'Black Elves\'.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "Klingons express emotion in art through opera and poetry.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "Bob Ross was a US Air Force pilot.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In \'Doctor Who\', the Doctor gets his TARDIS by stealing it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "The Klingon home planet is Qo\'noS.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "Klingons respect their disabled comrades, and those who are old, injuried, and helpless.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "Like his character in \'Parks and Recreation\', Aziz Ansari was born in South Carolina.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In \'Star Trek\', Klaang is a typical Klingon male.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Television",
     "question": "In \'Star Trek: The Next Generation\', Data is the only android in existence.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}
]
